Fear will find you.
Hidden is a thriller, horror film directed by Ross Duffer.
A family takes refuge in a fallout shelter to avoid a dangerous outbreak.
Ray, played by Alexander Skarsgård.
Claire, played by Andrea Riseborough.
Zoe, played by Emily Alyn Lind.
Jillian, played by Heather Doerksen.
Joey Neary, played by William Ainscough.
Breather Lieutenant, played by David James Lewis.
Hidden is a 2015 American  psychological thriller film written and
directed by the Duffer Brothers in their feature film debut.
The film stars Alexander Skarsgård, Andrea Riseborough, and Emily Alyn Lind.
This was producer Richard D.
Zanuck's last film; he died before filming began.
Hidden was released in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on September 15, 2015.
The film received a few positive reviews from
critics and grossed $310,273 worldwide.
The film explores themes of helicopter, quarantine,
nightmare, underground, shelter.
The tone is dark and intense.